#### **CHANGHAO LI**

changhaoliurban@gmail.com | (267) 403- 7980 | https://changhaoli.com

### **OBJECTIVE**

Master of City Planning students (2nd year) with four years of experience in landscape architecture and one year of experience in city planning and urban design. Seeking full time job and internships in urban planning and Spatial data analysis.

#### **EDUCATION**

## The University of Pennsylvania, Weitzman School of Design

Expected May 2023

Master of City Planning, Concentrations in Urban Design

Beijing Forestry University (BJFU), Beijing, China

Sep 2015 – Jun 2020

Bachelor of Agriculture, Concentration in Landscape Gardening

GPA: 3.55 / 4.0

#### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

Programming Skills: R, Python, C++, Git, Arduino IDE, NetLogo, Microsoft Office

Design & Analysis Software: Adobe, AutoCAD, SketchUp, Rhino, Grasshopper, Lumion, Vary, Arc GIS, Geo Data

Mathematics: OLS, Geographically Weighted, Logistic, Time-Series, Cross-Sectional Regression

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Economic Development Techniques**

UPenn, United States

TA Intern

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

 Assisted the instructor in developing and grading R-based assignments, which focused on analyzing the urban population and economy

### **China Northwest Architecture Design and Research Institute**

Xi'an, China

Planning Intern

Mar 2021 - May 2021

Bashan village planning project, Hanzhong, China

- Designed public square with a focus on the preservation of historical building and made the master plan and the graphic renderings with CAD and Photoshop.
- Investigated the local native plants and used CAD to make the planting design

Kangle county planning project, Linxia hui autonomous region, China

- Developed land use plans that comply with territorial spatial planning standards.
- Analyzed site area data by GIS and Proposed improvement programs to meet the requirements of town governments

#### RELEVANT COURSEWOTK & PROJECT

CPLN 6710 Statistical and Data Mining Methods for Urban Data Analysis

UPenn, United States

Instructor: Brusilovskiy, Eugene

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

• Utilized statistical regression analysis and R programming to predict median home values in Philadelphia, and examined the impact of alcohol consumption on traffic accidents.

CPLN 675 Land Use and Environment Modeling

UPenn, United States

Instructor: Michael Fichman

Feb 2022 – May 2022

- Developed a fishnet model in GIS to analyze flood risk in Calgary. Utilized R to test and train the model, and applied the calibrated model to predict flood-prone areas in Denver.
- By analyzing the extent of regional development, use GIS and R studio to predict the impact of new urban planning on the spatial distribution of the city resources

#### **HONORS & AWARDS**

- University-level Merit Student, Beijing Forestry University, 2019
- Student Scholarship, Beijing Forestry University, 2016-2017 & 2017-2018 & 2018-2019